Guide to the Edward Ginzton Papers SC0330
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1998-231
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Text and Program, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee, Aetna (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Primco 1990, October-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Primco 1990, March-April (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- New Bold's (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Columbus Circle Investors (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Prudential, J 984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- Prudential, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- T. Rowe Price, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee- T. Rowe Price, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - V.A.- Executive Committee, May 1994- November 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - V .A.- Finance Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - V.A.- Finance Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - V.A.- Finance Committee, 1988 (February-June) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - V .A.- Finance Committee, 1988 (August-December) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - V.A.- Board of Directors Briefing Book, February 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - V.A.- Revisions to Board of Directors Handbook 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - V.A.- Form I 0-K, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - V.A.- Form 10-K, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - V.A.- Form 10-K, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - V.A.- Fom1 10-K, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - V.A.- Corporate Response Plan (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - V.A.- Technology and Environmental Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - V.A. -Board of Directors Social Security Numbers (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - V.A.- V.A. Correspondence J. Tracy O'Rourke, 1990 January-May (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - V .A.- Correspondence J. Tracy 0' Rourke, 1990 June- 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - V .A.- Correspondence Craig Nunan, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - V.A.- Nominating Committee (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - V.A.- Non-Citizen Board Members (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - V.A.- Strategic Planning Presentation (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - V.A.- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - V.A.- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - V.A.- Executive Biographies A-M (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - V.A.- Executive Biographies A-M (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - V.A.- Executive Biographies N-Z (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - V.A.- Instrument Group, Strategic Alternatives Task Force (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - V.A.- "A Study on the Future of the NMR at Varian (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - V.A.- Retirement and Profit Sharing Program (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee Annual Report to the Board of Directors (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - V.A.- Gary Simpson (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - V.A.- Chronological File, July-December 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - V.A.- Board of Directors Handbook, Revised 1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - V.A.- Stockholders' Annual Meeting, 198 1-1 992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - V.A.- Form 10-K, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - V.A.- Miscellaneous Related Articles and Reports (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - V.A.- Shieds vs. Battaglia, et. al (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - V.A.- Technology and Environmental Committee (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - V.A.- Correspondence/ Memos (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - V.A.- Correspondence/ Memos (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - V.A.- Correspondence/ Memos (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - V.A.- Correspondence/ Memos (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - V.A.- Annual Reports 1991-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - V.A.- Annual Reports 1988-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - V.A.- Corporate Strategy Assessment (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - V.A.- Corporate Strategy Assessment (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - V.A.- Project Change, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - V.A.- Retirement and Profit Sharing Program (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Varian/ S.V. History (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reprint (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Oral History/ Autobiography (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Oral History/ Autobiography (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Correspondence 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ginzton Paper at S.U.A. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - File Inventory (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Klystron's to S.U. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ginzton Biography (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ginzton- Outgoing Letters (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Varian- Old Timers (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Autobiography/ Oral History (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Autobiography/ Oral History (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Autobiography/ Oral History (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Parkington's Foundation (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Unknown Mailing Lists (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Power Tube Follies (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Adams, Ansel (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Mail Logs (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Speech at SLAC Anniversary 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - China- Xie Jialin (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - China- Professor Yang Shiquin (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Club of Rome (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ginzton Interview by Sharon Mercer (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Book Stuff (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Book Stuff (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Book Stuff (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Book Stuff (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Assorted Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 38)